CURRICULUM VITAE

Originally from Vietnam, I have been living and studying in the Netherlands on and off for 30 years. I am always looking out for entrepreneurial mindsets to learn from, as well as people who share my fascination for technology integration and innovation in daily lives and business strategies.

I have a multicultural background, gained through my working and living opportunities in various great international settings. This background provides me necessary skills to engage effectively in communication and relationship management. I have also worked within different domains, which have always helped my communication skills tremendously with different stakeholders as a data analyst/scientist.

I do not shy away from challenges and unfamiliar terrains. To me, they are windows of opportunities to learn and to grow.



Personal Details

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

Name : Lan Yen Dao Nguyen Date of birth : 13th April 1990

Address : Strevelsweg 103B01

3073 DW, Rotterdam

Nationality : Dutch

Mobile No. : (+31) 6 1499 1537

Email

lanyendaonguyen@gmail.com

LinkedIn profile

www.linkedin.com/in/lanyendaonguyen

September 2015 – December 2017
MSc. specialization Data Science:
Business and Governance
Tilburg University

September 2009 – October 2013

BSc. International Business and

Management Studies in Rotterdam

University of Applied Science

September 2005 – June 2009 Diploma Le Quy Don High School Ho Chi Minh City – Vietnam **Skills**

Extract, Transform, Load (ETL)

Python, R, SQL Power BI, Tableau

Machine Learning models

Alteryx

Microsoft Office
Adobe Photoshop

Docker

SKILLS & COMPETENCIES

Personal Hobbies

Git, Bitbucket

Google Cloud Platform (Big Query)

Wordpress, Prestashop

Agile Scrum Languages

Vietnamese: Native proficiency

English: Professional working proficiency

Dutch: Intermediate proficiency

Creating and editing own videos, digital art

designs.

Very interested in Equity management, Investments (both in real estate and stocks). Enjoys a good horror, thriller and adventurous

book or movie. A Linkin Park fan.

Loves to experiment with cooking and have

people tasting.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Data Scientist/Data Analyst at Media Markt NL (November 2019 – present)

- Conduct customers' insight analysis automated reports that combines data from multiple sources (Big Query, Teradata, MSSQL)
- Analyze historical CRM data to recommend Media Markt's fiscal year KPI targets.
- Create weekly customer target groups for specific campaigns.
- Full-stack develop insights Club Member and Campaign KPI performance reports for all 52 Media Markt outlets, in which the recommended fiscal year targets are integrated.
- Support digital marketing team setting up automatic email type processes.

Junior Developer/Data Analyst at The Feedback Company (August 2018 – October 2019)

- Support, maintain, and creating new features for Feedback Company's ecommercial plugins.
- Design, implement and maintain KPI reports, and insights dashboards for business decisions.
- Creating ETL pipelines for different data analysis reports, this ensures seamless integrations between the database with processed data and external applications such as Power BI.
- Building and maintaining data services that enable stakeholders to leverage that data and drive business insight and decisions.

Policy & Research Officer at ABN AMRO Escrow & Settlement (June 2016 - September 2016)

- Worked as an assistant with daily reconciliations
- Performed KYC and KYC's business, compliance tasks.
- Performed background and security screenings of clients

- Gathered and processed legal documents of individuals and companies for screening.
- Worked closely with Client Due
 Diligence for the process of screening clients

PR & Event project assistant for Holland Village (April 2013 – November 2013)

- Worked closely with the organization board members for PR campaigns and sponsors.
- Executed contracts and communication with suppliers, contractors and sponsors.
- Negotiations and strategic planning
- Sponsorship packaging development
- Kept track with the organization timeline
- Supervised with the construction of the event.

Organized by the Consulate General of The Kingdom of The Netherlands in Vietnam I joined the board members for Holland Village 2013 as project assistant. The project was to celebrate 40 years of diplomatic relations between Vietnam and The Netherlands in the framework of "Trade and Sustainability". More than 20 Dutch organizations supported and participated in Holland Village 2013, which presented over 40 activities and programs of seminars, networks informative activities for more than 10 days.

Accounting assistant at Merlin Entertainment Australia (2011 – 6 months)

- Daily Journals and reconciliations
- Monitored organization's daily income cash flow and allocated the cash inflows in different categories.
- Monitored the balance and identified for logical explanations.
- Invoices and vouchers handling
- Preparation of admission dossier, send invoices to companies and handle refunds for customers if necessary.